<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Usage examples on AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper</title>
    <link>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Usage examples on AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Authelia with LDAP-wrapper</title>
      <link>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/authelia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/authelia/</guid>
      <description>Authelia supports LDAP authentication, enabling users to log in by authenticating against your LDAP directory. This guide outlines the steps to set up LDAP authentication with Authelia using LDAP-wrapper.&#xA;Prerequisites Settings for Authelia LDAP Authentication with LDAP-wrapper Prerequisites&#xD;Before configuring LDAP authentication for Authelia with LDAP-wrapper, ensure the following prerequisites are met:&#xA;LDAP-wrapper: Ensure you have a functioning LDAP-wrapper. Authelia: Set up and configure Authelia for your environment. Settings for Authelia LDAP Authentication with LDAP-wrapper&#xD;To configure LDAP authentication with Authelia using LDAP-wrapper, follow these steps:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portainer</title>
      <link>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/portainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/portainer/</guid>
      <description>Portainer supports LDAP authentication, allowing users to log in by authenticating against your LDAP directory. This guide outlines the steps to set up LDAP authentication over LDAP-wrapper with Portainer.&#xA;Prerequisites Settings for Portainer LDAP Authentication with LDAP-wrapper LDAP Configuration LDAP Security User Search Configurations Prerequisites&#xD;Before configuring LDAP authentication for Portainer, ensure the following prerequisites are met:&#xA;LDAP-wrapper: Make sure you have a working LDAP-wrapper. Portainer: Install and set up a working instance of Portainer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synology Radius with UniFi</title>
      <link>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/synology-radius-unifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/synology-radius-unifi/</guid>
      <description>UniFi allows you to use a custom Radius server like the default package from Synology. Combined with the LDAP-wrapper, this creates a powerful setup for your users.&#xA;DSM 7.2.1-69057 Update 3&#xA;LDAP-wrapper v2.0.2&#xA;RADIUS Server Package 3.0.25-0515&#xA;UniFi Network Application 8.0.24&#xD;Prerequisites Settings in Synology RADIUS Server Settings in UniFi Controller Prerequisites&#xD;Before configuring Synology Radius and UniFi, ensure the following prerequisites are met:&#xA;Synology NAS: Ensure you are up to date with your DSM, and install the current RADIUS Server package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>user-reported examples</title>
      <link>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/user-reported-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ahaenggli.github.io/AzureAD-LDAP-wrapper/usage/user-reported-examples/</guid>
      <description> Using the wrapper to get a Sophos firewall to authenticate VPN users with AzureAD </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
